achievacu.com 2005-11-09

# Privacy Pledge

Our Privacy Pledge  
  
Achieva Credit Union, a member-owned financial institution, is committed to protecting your privacy. 

1\. We do not sell your personal information to anyone.

2\. Information we collect about you.

In the course of doing business with us, you routinely provide personal information that is not available publicly. This includes information we receive from you on applications and other forms, information about your transactions with us, and information we receive from consumer reporting agencies. Examples include your name, address, social security number, telephone number, income and account balances. 

We use this personal information to service your accounts, underwrite your loans and offer you other products and services to meet your needs. We collect only the information necessary to provide you with accurate, reliable service.

3\. Information we share with service providers.

From time to time we will share some of your personal information with non-affiliated companies that perform services for us or with whom we have joint marketing agreements. For example: we provide your name, address and transaction data to the company that prints and mails monthly account statements. We may also share your name and address with the company that mails our newsletters, or with a company through which we jointly market insurance or other products. In all such cases, we share only the information necessary to accomplish a specific task.

4\. We safeguard your personal information.

We obtain a written agreement prior to sharing personal information with any non-affiliated company. They are contractually committed to uphold our strict standards of confidentiality and to limit use of this information to its intended purpose only.

Within the Credit Union we restrict access to information about you to only those employees who must know the information to provide products and services to you. We maintain strict physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.

5\. Lifetime guarantee.

We will apply our strict confidentiality policy for as long as we retain your personal information, whether or not you remain an active member of your Credit Union.

Our relationship is built on trust. You can be confident that your financial privacy is a top priority at Achieva Credit Union.  

How We Protect Your Online Information

All account activity conducted through our website — including online account access, bill payment and loan/credit applications — is protected by state-of-the-art encryption and firewall technology.

What You Can Do to Help Us Protect Your Privacy

Achieva Credit Union is committed to protecting the privacy of our members. You can help by following these simple guidelines:

  * Protect your account numbers, card numbers, PINs (Personal Identification Numbers) and passwords. Never keep your PIN with your ATM/debit or credit card, in case your card is lost or stolen.
  * Use caution when disclosing your account numbers, social security numbers, etc. to anyone. If someone calls you, explains the call is on behalf of the Credit Union and asks for your account number, you should beware. Official Credit Union staff will have access to your information and will not need to ask for it.
  * Keep your information with us current. It is important that we have up-to-date information on how to reach you. If we detect potentially fraudulent or unauthorized activity or use of an account, we will attempt to contact you immediately. If your address or phone number changes, please let us know so we may update our records.

Leaving Our Site

Clicking on any of the links provided on this site will cause you to leave this website, and will take you to an alternate web site that is not operated by Achieva Credit Union (Credit Union). The Credit Union is not responsible for the content of alternate sites and does not represent either that party or you, should you enter into a transaction on an alternate site. Privacy and security policies associated with alternate sites may differ from those practiced by the Credit Union.   

If you have any questions concerning this privacy pledge, please do not hesitate to call us - we are here to serve you.

Achieva Credit Union  
10125 Ulmerton Road  
Largo, FL 33771  
(727) 431-7680 Main Phone Number  
(727) 431-7680 Member Service
